Hi everyone this is Professor
I am a marine biologist at Saudi between diversity and I study sociology and it's part of my job
New York state water
So today I am on a fishing boat in Long Island Sound right now let's go back to the campus
Welcome to the lab
In this session
You'll get familiar with oyster external and internal anatomy
And you'll receive a hands-on experience of some of the diagnostic
Effectively
While I will be dissecting my colleague Nora would be narrating the Portugal
Let's start with some tool you will be using during this procedure
Syringe and needles
Clam shucking knife
Scissor tweezers and a cell phone
Easter oyster
Castle Story of rajinikanth
One of the most important species of 5l
Along the coast of the US
Including
Virtue shells are not identical
All the bottom or
Oysters
Top or right is flat
Now
NYC Dedenne
Open the area where the shows are connected
Right side of the right shell
Well the left side
Exterior
The mountains located Adventure your end of the animal
All the rectum is located at the posterior
Looking at the Shell
It is possible to see artifacts including worm to attach to the Shell
Tommy Dorsey
What is not rare small holes left by sponges. Colonize the show
To open our stuff to order we will be using the hinge entry
Shocking message
First athlete to do
Mission oyster
They are joined at the hip
Recursively oriented
Move the blank forward along the flat right show
The right show
When the muscle has been inside
Will Barton
Knowledge preschool Easter on a flat surface and Truckin
Twisting motion slightly apart
Monster Blade along the fox show and cut the adductor muscles
Predictably pressed up against the inner top surface of the right cell
Now you can gently pry the top show away from the bottom shell with a knife
Pull the right shell completely off
Notice the position of the adductor muscle
Insides of the right show
The different organs of the oyster
The first issuing currency is the mantle
The mantle produces the shell and covers the internal organs
It's always in contact with the shells
But not attached to them
Region of the oyster we can identify a large organ called
Adductor muscle
Apart
Enlarging PC
The other smaller and wider
Your muscle functions to close
Oyster shell
Observe the pericardial cavity
Pokemon
Remembering part of the animal
You will need a one milliliter syringe and a 22 gauge needle
For educational purposes we are going to collect the humans directly by punching a hole
Pericardial cavity
Observed using a microscope
Video shows you how old sterzing on sides
Daigo Saito size plastic beads added to the preparation
Who sells playing portent roll in oysters
Can you describe an oyster Anatomy
Mantle
Joker the largest organ in the oysters body
Consist of Four soldiers
Along with the mantle
What is the chief organ of respiration
Create water currents
Coalescence Orchard particles and move food particles to the lab for further sorting
Also serve two separate masses of eggs released from the ovary during spawning into individual over for fish and fertilization
We can observe the land fuel pump
Consists of two pairs of large sauce
Have a roughly triangular shape
Organs are known to control them total amount of food ingested
Assorted before ingestion
Unwanted material are rejected as
Little Caesars
Your mouth is located between the
This area corresponds to the visceral Mass including the stomach
Attract animals
The rectum along the adductor muscle
Extreme vetting
In order to determine if the oysters are infected with the parasite
Arkansas Marina
We will collect and incubate pieces of tissue
Specific culture media called
SPM
Starsector small piece of mantle
This area is particularly important because so don't see she's thinking pathogen cells accumulate there
For being rejected in the environment
Cells use this advantage to penetrate oysters
The small piece is been placed in the food containing SPM
Archangel spells can also accumulate at the end of the rectum
A little peace as well
Marinas needs lipids turn white
Avoid the proliferation of bacteria and fungus removal add antibiotic
Fungus to the media
Will then be stored for one week in the dark
Room temperature
Put on house sign gnostic
People realize
Cross section
The animal
After sectioning the adductor muscle and removing an oyster from its shell
People use a stopwatch
Find Flight of the digestion plant
Watch make sure we also include the mantle and do
Now
Alcohol before being invested in person
Cut into very fine sections for further microscopic observations
Are oysters